[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On January 19, 2006 NASA launched the unmanned mission New Horizons to explore Pluto, on a one-way trip of how many years?", "correct_answer": "9", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "15", "13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the book on which Soylent Green was based?", "correct_answer": "Make Room! Make Room!", "incorrect_answers": ["Soylent Yellow/ Soylent Green", "What is Soylent Green?", "In the Year 2022"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What science studies all aspects of wine and wine making?", "correct_answer": "oenology", "incorrect_answers": ["oology", "aetology", "oenophilia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1666 the first legal document to mention cheese was issued in Toulouse and it referred to what sort of cheese?", "correct_answer": "Roquefort", "incorrect_answers": ["Fromage Frais", "Gouda", "Brie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On average, how much of a persons body weight is muscle?", "correct_answer": "40%", "incorrect_answers": ["15%", "65%", "90%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Members of the Special Air Service of the British Army are forbidden to eat only this type of meat.", "correct_answer": "Rat", "incorrect_answers": ["Eagle", "Snake", "Pigeon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bacteriophages are organisms that have the characteristics of both viruses and bacteria.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Used to measure the concentration of sugar in wine, this scale was developed by a French pharmacist.", "correct_answer": "baume scale", "incorrect_answers": ["beaufort scale", "brix scale", "scoville scale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which US President invented the baseball seventh inning stretch?", "correct_answer": "Taft", "incorrect_answers": ["Hoover", "Wilson", "Harding"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote, directed, and starred in the 1981 movie The Four Seasons?", "correct_answer": "Alan Alda", "incorrect_answers": ["Glen Ford", "Robert DeNiro", "Len Carriou"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Grizzly bears can be found in Europe and North America.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert De Niro gained 60 lbs. during mid-shooting of Raging Bull to convert himself from the young muscular boxer to the fat, washed up person his character becomes.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]